# CHRISTAN DE LUNA

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Atlanta, GA cjdeluna95@gmail.com (770) 910-2701 linkedin.com/in/christan-de-luna github.com/cdeluna95 cdeluna95.github.io

## **SUMMARY**

A highly driven college graduate with two years of experience in information technology, specializing in software development. Up-to-date with the web development industry, with demonstrated ability to create exquisite user interface and user experience design, while continuously improving back-end skills and adhering to best coding practices to meet the goal of becoming a full-stack developer. Excels as an individual contributor and in a collaborative team setting to ensure work efficiency and punctual delivery.

## **EDUCATION**

#### B.S. Information Technology (Software Development)

Georgia Gwinnett College – Lawrenceville, Georgia

Awards: Dean's List, President's List, Magna Cum Laude

Coursework: Advanced Programming, Advanced Databases, Web Development, Software Development, Software Testing & QA

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Web Developer Intern

Turner Broadcasting System – Cartoon Network

January 2018 – May 2018

December 2017

GPA: 3.76

- Performed a series of data migrations from a fully Java-based back-end to a Drupal CMA as part of Turner's initiative.
- Integrated Conviva's SDK on website's video player by interacting with its API and constructing a series of metadata objects.
- Implemented complex security protocol changes on CartoonNetwork.com ahead of the Chrome 68 update.
- Converted PSDs manually to front-end code by employing responsive web design on CartoonNetwork.com's Drupal site.
- Accomplished game launches, page updates, and various minor enhancements to aid in the development process.
- Worked in an Agile environment using Scrum and JIRA to collaborate with cross-functional teams.

#### Web Developer Intern

January 2017 – August 2017

#### Turner Broadcasting System – Adult Swim

- Assisted in the development of weekly homepage updates and other webpages related to company shows and streams.
- Employed AJAX to interact with the Turner API and fetch data related to drawings submitted by visitors on the homepage.
- Implemented an interactive list of Adult Swim's projects with Vue.js in class-based syntax instead of just HTML and CSS.
- Performed QA tests on video player to ensure proper functionality, browser and device compatibility, and ad delivery.
- Accomplished data management in internal CMS, daily chat moderation, and online search of unwanted bootleg links.

#### WordPress Developer Intern

September 2016 – October 2016

#### Innovagears

- Developed, designed, and optimized client's website with WordPress and common web technologies.
- Used BugHerd to effectively communicate with the client, track assignments, and keep work flow going.

## **PROJECTS**

### Suri (Vue.js & Laravel)

August 2017 – December 2017

- Used Axios and promises to send AJAX requests, consume REST API, and perform CRUD operations on student data.
- Configured routes with vue-router to update dashboard pages dynamically without reloads from the server.
- Designed the user interface and user experience in clean SASS with minimal Bootstrap.

#### Xenoblade Chronicles Quiz (AngularJS)

December 2016

• Built a quiz app on the front-end, and fetched hardcoded-JSON data to load questions and answers.

#### Visual App (Ruby on Rails)

February 2016 - April 2016

Leveraged in-class knowledge and external resources to develop a visual image hosting app in a complete SDLC methodology.

### SKILLS

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP, Ruby, SQL

Technologies: Bootstrap, SASS, LESS, ES6+, jQuery, Vue, Laravel, Rails, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Oracle

Tools: Git, NPM, Bower, Gulp, Webpack, Heroku, AWS, S3, WordPress, Drupal, Photoshop, Google Analytics, GitHub, JIRA

Concepts: Algorithms, Data Structures, OOP, SDLC, Agile, Scrum, UI/UX/Responsive/Graphic Design, SEO

Certifications: Microsoft Technology Associate: Networking Fundamentals, Oracle Database 11g: SQL Fundamentals I